Captain?
Sir.
Well, that's not exactly a view
of the Afghani desert, ain't it?
But I understand there's a Chick-Fil-A
right within arm's reach so there's that.
It's a beautiful office, sir.
Thank you very much.
Captain, I'd like to suggest
you decorate the place.
Make it a little more homey, okay?
A lot of the soldiers
returned from deployment
where they've seen a lot of shit.
Excuse my French.
- Yes, sir, I completely understand.
And I promise to do
everything in my powers
to help these brave heroes
and get them back on track
to healthy civilian lives.
- Good.
So if there's anything
you need, anything at all,
I'm just a couple hallways away.
Yes, sir.
- Hey Jake.
- Brian.
- Good to see you, man.
Megan, how you doin'?
Hey, good.
- Do I have any more
appointments for the evening?
- Yes, I was actually
getting ready to call you up
because you do have one more.
I just have to confirm his details.
- You know what, I'll take it from here.
- Oh no, it's no problem.
I mean I just have to-
- No, I insist.
Thank you.
- Okay.
You sure?
- Yeah, enjoy your weekend.
If you insist.
Have a good day, sir.
- You as well.
Thank you for your patience.
- Please, I just wanted to drop by,
see how things are going.
I just wanted to make sure
everything's going smoothly on the inside.
- Right this way.
- Mmm, that is so happy.
So, did she finish the dress?
- Mhmm.
It's so beautiful, so perfect.
It's more beautiful than I
ever could have imagined it.
Ah, I'm so excited!
- Hey, I'm sorry that I can't be there.
- Mhmm, I'm sorry too, Missy.
So not okay.
Seriously, how's your mom doing?
- The doctor's are changing
up the medication again.
We just have to wait and see.
I am so happy for you though.
You don't even know how good you got it.
A great man, a happy family, a fun life.
- My life?
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
I mean I wouldn't call it perfect,
but after so long,
everything's finally going
in the right direction, you know?
Brian and I just put in
an offer on the house.
So we can finally say goodbye
to the landlords here.
- Right, if anyone deserves it, it's you.
Everything you've been
through, losing the baby.
Ugh, Tara, I'm such an idiot.
I'm so sorry, Tara, I
shouldn't have brought it up.
I should have just been happy for you.
- No, it's okay.
Hey, Jules, it's okay.
You're still my best friend.
Hey, I still love you okay?
Hey Jules, I need to let you go.
I think those are the cards.
Yeah, I need to let you go.
Bye, I love you, talk to you later.
Mwah mwah mwah, bye.
Hi.
Are these the cards?
- You need to sign.
- Okay.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, right there.
Great.
There you go.
- Okay, thank you so much.
What the fuck?
Hello?
Is there anyone out there?
Oh my god!
Someone help me!
What the fuck is this?
Help!
What's happening to me?
Why is this happening to me?
- I give people pills and tell them
to call me in the morning.
I don't actually help people.
- Yeah.
Yeah it's the best feeling
in the world, actually.
Helping people overcome their fears,
dealing with their inner demons.
- You're kinda like a priest,
exorcising demons.
- Brian, the demons aren't real though.
It's just in their minds.
I help them correct their thought process,
force them to face reality,
or my interpretation of it.
It brings them peace.
- Well the point is you help people.
- You really think so?
Hello?
Who are you?
What do you want?
Please let me go,
just let me go please.
- Shh.
In good time.
All in good time.
- Can I use the bathroom?
- Your chain will reach to the bathroom.
You're not an animal.
Yet.
- I don't know who you are
but you have the wrong person.
Please let me go, please.
Please.
I won't tell anyone, I won't.
- I'll pull your fucking tongue out.
- Please let me go, please.
Please let me go.
- In time.
In time.
All in good time.
- No, no, no.
No, no, no, please, please, please!
Please, no, no!
Please!
No!
I just want to be out!
Everything was perfect.
♪ Place of you ♪
♪ I can feel ♪
♪ I can see ♪
♪ With you ♪
♪ And if I had it all ♪
♪ I'd have nothing at all ♪
♪ If I don't have you ♪
♪ And baby when I fall ♪
♪ I won't fall so hard ♪
♪ Coz I'll fall with you ♪
- At least I have water.
- Tara?
What did she buy now?
Oh.
Wow.
How sweet.
Hm.
- Come on, you can do this.
You can do this.
Are you sure about this?
- Yes, I'm sure.
I have plenty of options.
With my credentials, there's
gonna be a local clinic
or a hospital that can use my experience.
Besides, most of these doctors
that are fresh out of medical school,
they can't really help
people that need help.
- Yeah, you're right about that.
But I don't know, I just,
I don't wanna be that guy
whose wife leaves everything for.
And I don't know, maybe 10, 20 years later
she resents him and kills him in the bed.
- Wait, wait, whoah.
Baby, hold up, hang on.
You think I'm going to
murder you in our bed
in 20 years time?
That's so cute, baby.
What do you think of me?
You know I can think of
a thousand ways to kill.
But bed, ugh.
It isn't one of them.
There's plenty of other
methods of homicide.
- How many do you know?
- Well I could poison you.
I could slip you a drug
that would slowly and cleanly
tear you apart from the inside,
leaving no mess at all.
I'm joking, baby.
Oh, come on.
You just have to know I
was an army psychologist
for so many years,
and yeah I've heard a lot of stories.
- I know you have.
- Well I wanna get out of it.
Open up my own practice.
I actually wanna help abused women.
When I'm more stable,
when we are more stable.
- Yeah, I get that, but,
I mean if you leave how do you know
if you're gonna be stable,
if we are gonna be stable?
You know, you never know.
I mean are you're really sure?
- Yeah.
Yes, I'm sure.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Yes, I am so sure.
I am so sure.
What did you learn at Camp McCall?
SEER.
Survival, Evasion, Resistance.
Escape.
The first moments are the most critical.
Try to escape before you become,
captured.
Once you become captured, your
chances of escape go down.
Your situation becomes
much more difficult.
You lose tenacity and fear takes over.
A weapon, you need a weapon.
Your mind, Tara.
Your mind is a weapon.
All those sessions with soldiers with PTSD
went way over the edge.
No other psychologist would
take them, but you did.
And did any of them ever harm you, no.
Because you used your head.
You controlled the situation.
The man who delivered the box.
You've seen him somewhere before, where?
Was he in the army?
Was he one of Brian's patients?
Did you run into him at the surplus store?
Think, Tara.
The man who delivered the box,
he's your first clue.
Don't give up.
Focus on something you can do.
Radio, get the radio.
Ah, fuck.
It's doubtful it would
be someone from the army,
you'd been out almost two years.
Next question, why.
Why would someone take you?
Use your training, Tara, think.
Why do people get kidnapped?
Think, think!
People get kidnapped for,
money?
Revenge?
Mental disorder like Norman from Psycho.
Physical torture and...
sex.
Women get kidnapped for sex,
for sex trafficking and
to become sex slaves.
Money, why wouldn't they take someone
with a more substantial income?
All of our money is going to student loans
and now the house,
and currency's going digital,
there's no way he'd get away with it.
You led a decent life.
You never intentionally
tried to harm anyone.
And you drive like an old lady
so road rage is out, revenge is out.
Wait now.
What about Brian's ex-girlfriend?
Oh no.
She's planning my bridal shower now.
This was too well planned out.
Mental disorder.
Even the craziest soldiers,
you treated them well.
And whoever did it has some
kind of medical background
because he knocked me out with something.
Physical torture.
No.
No, he left me food and water.
If he wanted to torture me
he'd make me beg for food and water.
Sex traffickers generally take women
who won't be missed.
And Brian will notice, Julie will notice.
But it has to be either torture or sex
and neither of those is an option.
Torture.
He'd beat me first.
He'd show me that he is the master
and I am the slave.
But both torture and sex,
they drug the victim first.
No.
You had to twist open the bottle
and the packages were sealed.
Okay, okay.
Sex, it has to be sex.
But why haven't they gang raped me yet?
It's the first step.
Second step.
First step is they drug the victim first.
But trafficking organizations
have a top age of 25
and I'm...
Evasion.
Your captors will deliberately
try to disorient you.
Think, Tara, think.
What do you recall before waking up here?
Think!
I don't know.
Not real.
I don't recall waking up here.
Help!
What are you doing, be quiet.
Do you want to get yourself killed?
Listen.
I don't hear anything.
Birds.
Birds!
I'm outside somewhere.
Outside somewhere where,
where no one can...
Why is this happening?
I don't know why this is happening to me.
I don't deserve this.
Article V of the US Military
Code of Conduct states
if your questioned should
you become a prisoner of war,
you're required to give your name, rank,
service number, and date of birth.
You will evade answering
any further questions
to the utmost of your ability.
If your captors want
information, play dumb.
You're just a lowly private
who doesn't know anything.
If you're higher ranking,
tell them that your aides
work out all the battle plans for you
and you don't know them yourself.
Hell, tell them you just make
the coffee in the office.
But above everything else, keep the faith.
You will escape of you will get rescued.
I don't understand.
But you will survive
and you will return home with honor.
What do you want?
Please tell me what you want.
Please.
- Do you know what "de opresso
liber" means, Cassandra?
- My name isn't Cassandra.
You've got the wrong person,
you're making a mistake.
- What's in a name anyway?
Today, right now.
At this very moment,
your name is Cassandra.
My name is Bruce.
Now.
Say your name.
- Cassandra.
- Good.
Have a pleasant night, Cassandra.
- Wait, Bruce.
Bruce.
What do you want?
I don't have any money.
Have I hurt you, do I know you?
I don't know any Cassandras,
you're making a mistake.
Please, just let me go.
Just let me go, Bruce, please.
- You will tell no one?
No one, no one, I swear to God.
I swear.
- Soon.
But not yet, Cassandra.
All in good time.
- Bruce, Bruce!
Wait, no, no!
Why am I here?
- We're here to help people.
- Sometimes I wonder whether I'm helping
anyone at all.
- Captain, you couldn't have known.
- No, I should have known.
He was my patient, I was
treating him, I was...
- You said it before, Captain.
We can't save everyone.
- But Eddie, I,
Eddie, I could have saved him!
- These soldiers are mentally unsound.
- No, it's my fault.
There was something I missed.
There was something...
- They undergo extensive training.
They're deprived of rest and food
for weeks on end.
Now he probably knew exactly
what you wanted to hear.
And Captain, he wanted to go back.
And that is not your fault.
- Colonel, sir, it is my fault.
It's my job.
I should have seen through his act.
I should have confirmed my suspicions
on his diagnosis way before
any of this happened.
I could have closed the gate on this.
He killed a whole team
of Afghan nationals.
And they never saw it coming.
They weren't there for the A-team.
You and I both know that.
They took it way beyond self-defense.
It was way beyond self-defense.
It was walking around with
their bloody intestines
all over his shoulders
and he was going to each-
- Captain!
Don't.
Please don't.
- Bruce said "de opresso liber".
To free the opressed.
Bruce was a green beret.
Or PSYOPs, he might be
doing this because of Eddie.
But why?
There's nothing to be gained.
I can't tell the army Eddie's okay,
it's too late for that.
Why?
- Because it will help you.
- The mission's classified.
- Yes, of course, Eddie, but
I do have the necessary
clearance for this and
everything we talk about
remains classified.
Look, you don't have to tell me anything
you don't wanna talk about.
Just tell me about how you're feeling,
what you're thinking,
so we can sort through this together.
- We.
I like the way you just did that.
- And what was that?
- The way you took my problem
and made it about us.
You're good.
But you're gonna somehow keep my demons
locked in the closet?
- You have to trust me, Eddie.
I'm really here to help you.
- Trust?
That's a good one, Doc.
You know, that's exactly what
we would say to the natives
whenever we would stroll
up in their village
wanting them to put
their lives in the line
to fight our war.
Trust us.
We are here to help.
You know like I know that's
nothing but bullshit.
We train them to fight.
Then when the president says it's enough,
we get to go home to America.
While those natives have
to watch their daughters
get raped and slaughtered
like fucking pigs.
- Eddie, you were doing your job.
You cannot believe that those people
were your responsibility.
Yeah, okay.
- Look, if it was really that bad
why do you wanna go back?
- Now there's a good question, good girl.
Because,
it's the only thing I know how to do.
And I'm very, very good at it.
- Okay, Eddie.
Why don't you tell me a little bit of
how you came to be on the Special Forces?
Tell me a little bit
about your family life.
Did you have any brothers and sisters?
What did your father do for a living?
Tell me a little bit about your mother.
Let me get to know you a little bit.
- We're gonna do this?
Four professions that I truly despise.
You wanna hear 'em?
Yeah.
- Okay.
One, attorneys.
Fucking hate 'em.
Two, doctors.
Three, good old car salesmen.
And four, my favorite of
the bunch, psychologists.
Because y'all think that
you know more than me.
And you believe in that
warped fucking mind
that I need your help.
I don't.
- Eddie, I'm here to help you.
- You read my file.
You know that I was orphaned
at the age of seven.
You know that I graduated
from high school with honors.
You know that I got a
Bachelor's Degree in Education.
And you also know that after three years
I joined the army.
And then after that, after two,
I was selected for green berets.
You know everything about me.
But you wanna sit there,
look me in my eyes
and play these little
fucking mind games with me
about how I'm feeling.
And whether the fact that
my father was a minister
is causing me to doubt what I'm doing.
Your fath-
My father,
was a mechanic.
But you already knew that.
Doc.
I'm tired of killing.
But it's all I know.
It's all I know.
- Eddie, I have read your file.
And I also know that you and your team
rescued many, many hostages.
You might have taken lives,
but you saved many, many more.
Lives that would have been lost
had you not been there.
You've done a lot of good.
- We have a motto in the Special Forces.
"De opresso libre".
To free the opressed.
You think about that.
- It has to be related to Eddie, but why?
The families of the soldiers?
Do they want revenge?
Eddie was also a part
of the Apsychological Operations Unit.
They were responsible for
using nonviolent means
to persuade enemy and neutral nations
to take actions that the
US Government wanted.
This is because of Eddie then.
Do they want me to talk?
Is this a trick?
If this isn't about Eddie and I,
don't use the radio then.
They'll torture, rape and kill me.
Is it worth the risk?
No, not yet.
Brian will call the police.
They'll interview the neighbors.
Mrs. Olson, the busybody,
she's always watching.
She will tell them that you got kidnapped.
She'll give them the license plate number.
The police will track the
vehicle to this location.
They will find you.
Just keep the faith, Tara.
Keep the faith.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah Brian's gonna find me.
I know it, I know it, he's gonna find me.
She's not at the house.
Do you know where she is?
You didn't get her text?
- No, no.
Well, no.
She said that
she decided to talk
to her former Colonel to
see about getting referrals.
Colonel Reeder
in North Carolina?
Yes, at Fort Bragg?
- But we were supposed to
see the venues this week.
She said that she'd
be gone at least three days.
- But why would she go
to Fort Bragg, I mean?
Clients.
The Colonel said he'd work up a list
of current and former military wives
who might be interested
in counseling sessions.
- Okay, um...
I shouldn't tell you
but she was hoping this would be something
of a wedding present.
She knows you spent a lot,
and she loves you more than anything,
you have to know that.
By the way, put the cards
in the refrigerator.
- All right, yeah, cool.
All right Julie, I'll talk to you later.
Thanks, bye.
Put the cards in the refrigerator?
- It shouldn't be this cold.
Don't be stupid, he's
using sensory torture.
And what makes you think he didn't plant
the radio there for you to use?
To get you to talk, to spill your secrets!
The radio was over there, it was hiding.
He probably didn't even know it was here.
He chained you to the RV floor,
of course he would have searched it.
Well if he thought this
was a temporary place,
maybe he didn't know.
Maybe he didn't know it was here.
But if I don't use the
radio and he comes back...
Don't think about what could happen.
Think about escape.
It's worth the risk.
It's your only chance.
Hello?
Hello, is there anyone there?
Hello, hello, is there anyone there?
Someone please an...
Someone please answer me.
Hello?
Hello, please, someone.
This is so stupid.
Yeah, I'm here.
- Hi, hi.
I need help.
Yeah, well don't we all?
- No, I'm serious.
I've been kidnapped.
Yeah sure, tell me another one.
- I'm being serious.
Somebody took me out of my apartment
and put me in an RV.
Oh, I get it.
You and your girlfriends are
taking a little road trip
in an RV, huh?
Well, radio's not a thing
to play around with.
Like, you teasing the guys, huh,
so get the hell off the air
and go tell your girlfriends that-
- I'm being fucking
serious, I got kidnapped!
Then call the cops!
- I don't have a phone.
You don't have a phone,
my five year old niece has a phone!
- I have a phone but it's in my apartment.
Would you please call the cops?
Sure, sure, yeah, yeah.
Let's start with the basics, okay?
What's your name?
- Tara, Tara Mays.
I'm Kenny.
But you can call me Kenny
but I'd prefer Bullet.
- Okay, thank you, Kenny.
Bullet, thank you, Bullet.
Where are you?
- I'm inside of an RV.
Yeah, you said that,
but where the fuck is the RV?
- I don't know.
Wait a minute.
You want me to call the cops
and tell them that you've been kidnapped
but I don't know where you are?
How the hell are they gonna find you?
No, no, no, no, see, this is how it works,
I call the cops, they'll make a record,
put my name on file.
Then when they can't find you
they'll put a note in my electronic file
saying that I'm a crank caller.
And then when I really
need the cops and call 'em,
these guys are gonna laugh
at me and just, you know?
- The police are gonna
interview my neighbors.
Talk to Mrs. Olson, she
would have seen something.
How old are you?
- I don't see how that fucking matters!
Are you over 18?
Then the cops are gonna say
you had a right to disappear.
They don't find any sign of
a crime at your apartment,
they'll just blow it off,
but you know, they'll know my name.
- Then don't give 'em your name.
Please, don't give them your name
but call the fucking cops now!
Hello?
Bullet, hello?
Bullet, are you still there?
Oh god.
You did it again, Tara.
When will you ever learn?
Roger, I completely
understand what you're saying.
Ah, fuck you too.
Sorry.
- We've both been in the same uniform and-
- Yeah?
But have you ever gotten
blood on your uniforms?
No.
Maybe a little of that sweet
sweat that runs down your back.
Ever killed anyone, Doc?
- Roger, there's many
people in the military
who perform invaluable duties, and
all of these which-
- You've never even thought
about killing someone, have you?
No.
- Okay Roger, we're here to talk about-
- Yeah I know, we're
here to talk about me,
I know, not what you think you've done
or what you think you're capable of doing.
I know, I get it.
So long as you
people have me locked up
in this godforsaken building,
rotting and waiting for what?
Yes, I kill people,
civilians, yes, I get it.
Right, isn't that why we're here?
Well yes, but I'm here-
- I killed those kids
because God only knows which
one of those little bastards
was gonna be a plant.
Had I not killed those kids,
and they'd gone on to kill the target,
my men could have died.
Get it?
- Okay Roger, I think we're gonna-
- And I will do it again.
Isn't that what you really wanna know?
Oh no.
You wanna know if I have nightmares.
Right?
And that if I'd do it again.
Nightmares about putting
rounds to the heads
of 10 year old kids.
And if I would do it again.
Yeah Doc, I would.
And no, I don't have nightmares.
I did what I had to do.
I did what I was trained to do!
You don't know shit.
- I do know something.
And I know we're not really here
because you protected your team.
We are here because of the allegations
of your sexual-
- You better watch your
fucking mouth, bitch!
I could kill you right fucking now
and there's nothing you
could do to stop me.
You, you don't know me.
- Roger please, I need you to calm down.
Things are gonna go a lot easier on you
if you do what I say.
- You killed me.
You killed me!
No.
That was not my fault.
- Of course it's not my fault.
From what you told me about Roger,
he's a real piece of work.
Psychopath, sociopath.
It's not your fault.
If it was anybody's fault,
it's the guards for having
not searched his cell.
- Roger hung himself
in his room yesterday.
And I didn't put him on suicide watch.
I didn't think he was self-destructive.
I didn't think he was gonna...
- You're given a certain amount of time
to get to know and come
to your conclusion.
But that's not your fault.
Maybe if you had more time
or fewer cases, but...
- No, I had enough time.
But my conclusion was wrong.
It's my fault that he's dead.
I should have known.
If Brian finds out,
he's never gonna trust me again.
He's always been so
skeptical about my work.
And now this is...
He doesn't think I'm
cut out to handle people
when I'm so...
When I'm so fragile myself.
Tara, baby,
dinner's about ready!
Baby, come away with me.
Leave that nutcase.
You can get out.
I can get my pension ready instead.
You and me, we'll live
off the grid together.
- Brian, that's not what you think.
- Hey, what's happening?
No, no!
No!
I don't wanna live, I don't wanna live!
Lay back, baby,
lay back baby, lay back.
Lay back, baby, lay back.
- It's not real.
You're just examining your life.
The bad things.
You have no idea where you are?
- No.
I don't know.
Right, anything in that RV
to show who owns it?
Maybe the photograph, name, registration,
something personal, something I can run
through the internet.
- I know I'm in a field, a remote field.
Oh, sure, little miss militia.
That narrows it right down.
I'll call the NSA right now
and have them pull up all
of their satellite photos
for empty fields.
Or why don't you just send
up a flare or something?
- Look, I'm trying, okay?
I'm trying.
Okay, okay, look.
Search around.
See if you can find
something in the RV, okay?
I'm gonna call some buddies
and see if they know anything.
I'll talk to you later.
- Wait.
Bullet.
Bullet, are you still there?
Okay.
Look around.
Timothy Harrison.
Laura Kennington.
Phone number.
You on the air?
- Bullet, yeah, yeah, I'm here.
Okay, so here's the deal.
No one has reported you missing.
- What?
What about Brian?
It hasn't been on the news, nothing?
Nothing?
Oh jeez Louise,
don't get your panties
in a knot, huh?
More hostages get themselves killed
when their captors figure out
that someone has reported them missing.
Count yourself lucky that no
one has reported you missing.
All right, now, did
you do like I told you?
Did you search the place, find some names,
something I can track down, anything?
- Yeah, yeah, I have names.
Timothy Harrison and Laura Kennington.
What kind of
fucked up name is Kennington?
- I don't know, British?
And I have a phone number.
208-558-4848.
Hmm, well
that's not a local number.
I'll check the area code.
- I have a street address.
6155 North Main Street.
You feel like
sharing the city with me?
- It doesn't have a city.
But it came with the phone number
so it should be whatever area code 208 is.
Wow, hey, you're sharp.
What else?
- E. Jennings.
Wow.
Now I wonder how many
E. Jennings there are.
Anything else?
- No, I stopped searching.
I couldn't find anything.
- At this very moment,
your name is Cassandra.
My name is Bruce.
- Wait.
Wait, he said his name was Bruce
and that mine was Cassandra.
Why the fuck
didn't you tell me that
to begin with?
- I don't know, I don't know.
I just thought of that right now.
Hey, you know what?
Why don't you try getting kidnapped
and having a chain on
your ankle, and, and...
What kind of chain?
It's important.
Everything you see, everything Bruce says,
it's all important.
Now what kind of chain?
Big links, small links?
And what kind of lock?
Combination or key?
- I don't know, it's a normal chain,
it's small links.
It's heavy.
And a key lock, an old key lock.
Like it's been used a lot.
He's had a lot of victims.
Okay, okay, I'll
run over what you gave me.
Just stay strong, I'll find ya.
- Thank you so much, Bullet.
I don't know what I would do
if I wasn't talking to you right now.
Listen, give me a few hours.
- Don't push him.
He's your only hope.
You have to trust me.
- I didn't do it.
- They have the other boot,
I found this one in your room.
- I didn't do it.
- George, the wear pattern on this boot
matches the one they have in evidence.
- I didn't do it!
- George, I'm trying to help you.
Before any of this happened,
I'm the one who helped you
deal with the loss of your son.
- What was that again?
Say that again?
You were here to help me when my son died?
You know how you helped me?
You told me everything
happens for a reason.
Now you tell me right now,
you tell me right now,
what is the reason for a
six year old boy to die?
- I can't help you if you don't help me.
When I testify, I will have to tell them
that you were under no stress.
There was no good reason
for you to kill your wife,
cut her up, and put her in the trash.
I didn't kill Veronica!
- They will give you the death penalty.
- Yes, it was my knife.
I know it was my knife,
but it wasn't me, you have to believe me.
I didn't...
Kill her.
- No one is going to believe you, George.
But if you trust me...
Tell me about how it
was your wife Veronica
who left your son alone.
George, tell me about,
tell me about all those
nightmares you've had
since his death.
Tell me about-
- Wait.
Are you asking me to lie?
- If you don't lie, you
don't have any hope.
He lied.
And I wrote my report.
And then they caught him in the lie.
And now poor George is
set to fry.
- Cassandra.
- Bruce?
- Good.
Very good.
- Please let me go.
Please.
- I need you to change.
- What?
Why?
- It's what I want.
- Please, tell me why
you want me to change.
- Because we're meeting friends.
- And you don't think
your friends will like me
in this dress, Brian?
- Babe, we're going to Applebee's,
not the Playboy mansion.
- I've had a bad day.
I've had a bad week.
It's been a bad fucking month.
The whole year's been fucking bad, Brian.
So I'm gonna wear this fucking dress now!
Sorry, baby.
How did I?
He's trying to wear you down with lights
and loud music.
Remember the story of Noriega in Panama?
He finally surrendered
after PSYOPS bombarded him
with lights and heavy metal music.
Why is he trying to break me?
Yo, Tara, you on the air?
- Yes, yes I'm here.
He was just here.
He's using lights and music and-
- Yeah, you know, I
try them too, with my dates.
You know, a little romantic
music, candlelight,
little some, you know, Kenny G.
Puts 'em in the mood.
- He's not trying to date me, Bullet.
- Oh, yeah, right, sorry, sorry,
didn't mean to.
- Have you found out
anything else about this guy?
What about the names I gave you, anything?
Yeah, but you won't like it.
- I don't care, tell me.
Sometimes what you
don't know won't hurt you.
- Got it, Kenny, just tell me.
Okay, you just remember,
I gave you the chance not to know.
- Please, just tell me.
Okay.
I'll start with the names you gave me.
Timothy Harrison,
he was five years old
when he went missing.
They never found him.
- How did he end up in here?
His family was
at a campground in Georgia.
Someone snatched him out of their tent.
- He used this RV to kidnap a child.
Laura Kennington,
she went missing
when she was 18.
She was camping with some
friends in Louisiana.
- He's using this RV to-
- Yeah, her
parents committed suicide,
or so they say.
A month after Laura went missing,
the neighbor found her
parents in their bedrooms
with bullet wounds in their heads.
- And you don't believe
it was suicide, why?
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, they left a note
saying some bullshit about
they had nothing to live for,
but I...
- But what?
They didn't find the gun.
You don't put a bullet in your head
then get up and you know, bury the gun.
They find the gun next to you.
- So you think he kidnapped Laura,
went back to her house,
picked up some things
and killed her parents?
That's what I would think.
- What about the phone number I gave you,
the street address?
It comes back to
an Idaho State Park Office.
The address looks like it
was a mail drop, you know?
Just a bunch of PO boxes,
but people were using
it as an office address.
- Idaho?
I looked at the State Park.
There'd been over 15 missing persons
since early 1990s.
All from that park.
- He's using that RV to...
Funny thing,
there was a park ranger
by the name of Emmett Jennings.
E. Jennings?
- So he's working with someone.
Well that's what it looks like.
- There's something you're not telling me.
What are you not telling me?
It's something
of an urban legend,
probably just a bunch of bullshit.
- Tell me.
Okay, here goes.
A couple of teenage girls reported
that they were camping around Jacksonville
and some older guy camped next to 'em.
At first, you know, he was helpful.
He said his name was Bruce
and said he had a teenage
daughter named Tiffany.
- His daughter's name is Tiffany.
Yeah.
Son's name was Billy and his
wife's name was Cassandra.
- Son's name was Billy,
his wife's name was...
He thinks I'm his wife.
Well he was in an old RV.
Anyway, the girls got into the RV
and he gave them some Mary Jane.
And they started to get stoned
and he started coming on to 'em.
The girls said that he told them
that he had been in the army.
Special Forces,
when he pulled out some
logging chains and a lock.
- So did they run?
Yeah, they ran.
Other people in the country have reported
seeing Bruce and the RV.
- Is that it, that's all to the story?
Well, I talked to some buddies
and they said Bruce is a collector.
- What does that mean?
Yeah, from what the girls said,
while Bruce was on Operation Desert Storm,
his family back in Iowa was killed
in a robbery gone bad.
- But his wife, his
wife's name was Cassandra?
Yeah, that's the story.
He's trying to collect the
family he lost, you get it?
Young son Billy, and the
teenage daughter Tiffany.
Fuck me.
I knew a Tiffany once,
she was smoking hot.
She had these tits that were sticking out.
- And the location of the RV?
Do you have any leads on where I am?
Look.
I don't want you to give up hope, huh?
You give up hope and that's
when you start thinking about...
- Putting a bullet through my head?
Well, you know what I mean.
I'm still checking on the information.
I'll find you, you gotta believe in me.
- Thanks, Bullet.
The only time you give up hope
is when you're dead.
Now stay strong, okay?
Keep the faith, I'll talk to you later.
- Okay.
Okay.
Turn off the radio and I'll
contact you at sunrise, okay?
- Yeah, yeah, sunrise.
Okay, so Bruce was in Special Forces.
You've counseled a lot
of Special Forces types.
Use what you know to find his weakness.
He lost a wife and son
while he was a soldier.
A young son and a teenage daughter.
The perfect family.
He thinks the army fucked him over
by not protecting them, play to that.
He might have his new wife
but you can tell him
where to get the children.
Play the role of the loving wife.
The Lima Syndrome,
where the abductor develops
sympathy for his hostage.
- He's not smart enough to win,
because he doesn't know me.
I know every mind game there is to know.
I'm gonna win.
You were absolutely brilliant, Frank,
detailing how it was the army
who turned you into a rapist
if in fact you ever were one.
I must admit, it was
one of my better ideas.
- What happens now?
- Well now, you get a
dishonorable discharge,
two years in a halfway house, and,
we continue our counseling sessions.
Congratulations, Frank, you're a free man.
- Free?
What about what I've done?
What about the victims?
- Well, a colleague of
mine who owed me a favor
conducted the interviews
of the alleged victims.
And, well I don't think the officers
of the current marshal board
were particularly pleased
to hear that the victims were,
for a lack of clinical terms, whores.
- But that doesn't make any sense.
- Frank.
You're free.
And based on my observations,
the local DA also agreed
that you will not be required
to either report or
register as a sex offender.
Now you can go out there
and get that daycare job.
Just like you always dreamed about.
- Really?
I'm really free?
- Yes, Frank.
You're really free.
- You know, I raped all those women.
They weren't whores.
But what I did to them,
that was nothing compared to
what I did to these children.
Free?
Maybe death will set me free.
- Frank, no!
You're a trained psychologist.
You have listened to sad stories
from hundreds of crazy people.
You can do this.
Because you're much smarter.
Okay.
- You were right, Doc.
I just need to see how it felt
and it felt fucking amazing.
- You fucking bitch!
You fucking bitch!
It will never fucking stop!
- Cassandra.
- Help me, help me.
- Mmm.
Baby.
You've really outdone yourself.
- Outdone myself?
Well I guess that's my ultimate
duty in this life, right?
To keep you completely satisfied.
- No.
No, that's not what I was saying.
Just, I loved dinner.
It was great.
It's good.
You were always a good cook, Cassandra.
You should eat while it's hot.
Unless you like eating those snacks.
Did the kids behave today?
- Oh, well, you know Billy,
he's six and he thinks he
should be driving already.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- And Tiffany, well she wants a new dress.
- Just like her mother.
- So.
You know, I've told you about my day.
About, well, Ms. Peterson
asking me to prescribe her
husband Viagra, you know
how that goes,
hopefully that never happens to us, but...
Anyways, let's talk
about you for once, hm?
How was your day?
- Really?
You know everything I do is classified.
Do you really wanna risk me losing my job
just so we can bond over them?
The look on
your face right now.
Bruce?
I think after breakfast,
we should take a drive like we used to.
- We never took drives.
You always got carsick.
You won't even go camping with me.
You said that's for redneck hillbillies.
- Really?
I never know when you're joking or not.
It's like you're just trying to play some
freaky mind games with me.
Walking on eggshells, not
knowing if I'm gonna offend you
or if I'm gonna say the wrong thing
and you're just gonna snap on me.
- I think after breakfast, which
you did a wonderful job at,
we need to go pick up Billy and Tiffany
from my sister's.
- Do you think I'm crazy?
- No, of course, not.
I'm just reminding you that
Billy and Tiffany spent
the night at my sister's
and we need to go pick them up.
- Tiffany was raped and gutted.
Billy was hung from the kitchen light.
They're both dead.
What?
- Look, Brian, you're a doctor, right?
And you treat the bodies of your clients.
Sort of like how a mechanic
works on a vehicle.
A mechanic?
No, I'm much more qualified
and higher above a mechanic.
- Whereas I treat the minds
of my clients.
- My pay grade is-
- Okay?
You can't see the mind.
- Skyrocketing fast.
- That makes diagnosis
a lot more difficult
than checking to see
whether Mr. Peterson's dick
is up or down.
It's hard, it's a trick.
- Okay, it's more complicated
than just looking at a dick.
- I have to know
everything about my client.
See, this is my party.
Not your party.
We do what I wanna do, not you.
You wanna play mind games?
Then I'll strip you naked,
bend you over this table, and
fuck you with a broomstick.
Best you eat this while it's hot.
What you don't eat, I will toss.
- Right, right, right.
You're giving me
- Why don't you shut up you
might just learn something.
- Fucking anxiety!
You're giving me anxiety.
Please, can we?
- You should fucking shut up
you actually learn something.
- Can we have
a normal conversation for once?
- No you be quiet,
and you shut up.
- We'll just have fun.
- If you fucking shut up you
would actually learn something.
What do you want?
- I want to eat my breakfast in peace.
Now eat.
Or get fucked.
It don't make no difference to me.
- You're so on edge all the time.
You're gonna make me blow
my fucking brains out.
- I wonder who would
be the worse for that?
Excuse me, I need some air.
- I'll have to blindfold you.
- Yeah that's okay, I just need some air.
If I promise not to look,
will you take the blindfold off?
- When I went to Kuwait,
they promise me that my
family would be safe.
Promises are like
toilet paper.
It's nice when you need it.
But when you wipe your ass,
the promise is covered in shit.
And it's only good to flush
along with all of the other shit.
- Very visual example.
Thank you so much for sharing.
- I think you've had enough fresh air.
Let's go.
Please let me go.
- I can't.
- I know where you can get a son
and a daughter.
And a much more beautiful wife.
- More beautiful than you?
- Yes, much more beautiful than me.
And she has a son and a daughter.
It's everything you want,
it's everything you've
been trying to find.
I can't have children.
- What's her name?
- Julie.
I can give you her address.
I can tell you how to get
to her and her children.
- We'll see, maybe.
- Yeah, that's it.
Give him something to think about.
Why go after the wife,
the son and daughter,
when you can get the whole family?
Bullet.
Kenny, Bullet, it's me, Tara.
Are you there?
I've been waiting all morning!
- Sorry, Bruce came in
and brought me breakfast.
Nice, nice, terrific.
I hope you enjoyed it.
Are you two planning a wedding?
- Do you have any information?
Any news on where the RV might be?
Please, anything, just
give me some good news.
This is the bad news.
Looking through the police reports,
- Police reports?
Yeah, listen, I
got a buddy on the inside.
Seems as though that RV is
something of a community vehicle
for serial killers.
Sorry, it's passed from one
serial killer to another.
Not that I'm scaring ya,
but if you believe in ghosts
then your RV should be packed full of 'em
'cause there's been a
lot of killings inside
and a lot of,
well you know, the stuff that
goes on before the killing.
- So you can't track its location?
That's a negative.
You're in a field, right?
Can you tell me something about it?
- He took me outside earlier
but I had something on my face.
Jeez, are you that ugly?
- Bullet, I couldn't see anything, okay?
Did you smell anything?
I don't know, like the smell of alfalfa,
corn, pig shit, something else to help.
Did you hear cows, maybe horses, anything?
- Amaranth.
I smelled Amaranth.
Everywhere I turned, I could smell that.
Amaranth?
Well if you smelled it
from every direction
then it could be a landscaper.
Okay, anything else?
Think, did you hear a train,
maybe a airplane flew over.
- Yes, yes, there was a airplane.
When?
- I don't know, 10 minutes ago.
And it was loud, like a commercial jet.
Okay, okay, this
is good, this is good.
A landscape business that raises Amaranth
and is in the flight
path of a commercial jet.
Think, use your head.
What else did you hear or smell?
- There were birds.
Like they were high above me.
But there were birds, lots of them.
Okay, okay,
okay, good, good, good.
A field bordered by tall
trees, this is good.
- Yeah, yeah, this is good.
Bullet.
Hey, Bullet.
Are you not telling me something?
What's going on?
You really wanna know?
- Yeah, yeah, tell me.
The way all these
serial killers, like Bruce,
have been able to keep killing people
is that they either hold their captive
for a maximum of four days
or they just move the RV.
- Are you saying I don't have much time?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Don't get all girly on me, okay?
I'll find you, don't worry about it.
But if you think he's gonna move the RV,
you gotta let me know, okay, like ASAP.
Do you hear me?
- Yes, I heard you.
All right, Jesus,
okay let me do some checking.
I'll hit you up at sunset
so don't turn off the radio, okay?
Just keep the faith,
it'll be okay, really.
- Okay, Bullet.
- Captain, I don't want you
to take this personally.
This is not a personal attack.
- Yes sir, I-
- But there seems to be
a pattern developing among the patients
that you're treating.
- Sir, I believe that-
- Let me finish.
Now I fully acknowledge that
since we began the war in Afghanistan,
the number of suicides
among returning veterans
has greatly increased.
But Captain, the majority of the soldiers
that you were treating,
let me be blunt.
You are one of the few counselors we have
that has a higher percentage
of suicides among the men they're treating
than non-suicides.
- Colonel, sir, respectfully,
you cannot be saying that
I'm not being successful.
I'm prepared to go through each
and every one of my patients
and provide a thorough
detailed explanation
for their psychological issues!
All of which might I add,
were pre-existing conditions.
- I don't think that-
- And in references to percentages,
you might want to consider that
as opposed to other counselors,
my caseload is predominantly
composed of operators
in the Special Forces Unit.
And being a member of
the Special Forces Unit
I might suggest already
indicate psychological issues.
- If one more of your
patients commits suicide,
I think it will be time for you
to start considering other options.
- Other options, sir?
What other options?
- You're young and you're talented.
Get out of the military.
Start a private practice, make some money.
But I can't keep trying to explain
how 90% of the soldiers
that you're treating
ends up committing suicide,
or hurting other people.
We're here to help them,
not push them over the edge.
Is that you, Tara?
- Kenny, is that you?
- No.
My handle's Pill Popper.
- What?
Bullet asked
me to make some research
and I think I've narrowed
down your location.
- You know where I am?
Yeah, but let me make sure
that Bullet told me right.
You can smell Amaranth on all four sides.
You're in a flight path,
and you can hear birds in tall trees.
Is that all right?
- Yes, yes, that's right, that's right.
This
actually makes more sense.
- It makes sense?
There's an
abandoned landscaping company
called Chamber's Cherubs.
They were one of the main
suppliers of Amaranth
until they went bankrupt.
They haven't been able
to sell the property
because it's located on a new flight path.
- So you know where I am?
I'm
looking at the aerial photo
and there's a wide open field
bordered by tall trees.
Looks like an old RV parked in the middle.
- That's me, that's me, that's me.
Call the cops please.
Please call the cops right now!
Darling,
I'd love to call the police.
See?
- Conspiracy nut jobs.
I'm dead.
- He's not gonna call the police,
he's not gonna call the police.
He fucking knows where I am,
he won't call the police!
Fucking idiots.
Sorry, sorry, can you say that again?
I'm sorry, I didn't hear that last part.
Can you say again?
Dead, I'm dead.
Not even an innocent, unborn
baby wanted to come out of you.
Your baby killed herself.
- The fuck?
Everyone
you know, you've killed.
- You killed me.
You killed me.
You
pushed them over the edge
playing your mind games.
Do it!
End the pain!
You'll be saving lives.
- What do you think?
- I think we just about
got our drug perfected,
that's what I think.
They keeping that same fucking name?
- Yeah.
- Well.
- People see what they wanna see.
And then they create reality based
on what they believe they see.
- Well I gotta tell you.
I really thought you blew your
fucking brains out out there.
- Is this drug working?
- Yes, the drug is infallible.
- I can't believe that she thought
you were gonna actually marry her.
That's unbelievable to me.
- Well, some people are too blind
to see the true reality.
She was never in an RV.
Only chained in her mind.
The drug blurs the lines between reality
and the perception of it,
allowing people to
inhabit false realities.
I'm surprised it worked so well
on a trained psychologist.
Someone who is supposed to see
through the lies of deception.
- Bruce!
De opresso de libre!
To free the opressed.
You know, the mind makes its own reality.
Makes its own terror, yeah.
Plays almost like a game.
- A mind game.